SUMMARY

Offering over five years' experience working in software development, web content management, eLearning courseware, web fundamentals coaching, and business operations.

I have a passion for creating inclusive experiences, relying on accessibility standards and user experience.

CONTACT

PHONE:

425-773-8165

WEBSITE:

victorswanberg.dev

EMAIL:

Victorswanberg89@gmail.com

SKILLS

Html, CSS, JS

People development

Web design

User experience

Wireframing

Mockups

FTP server

Continuous cloud integration

Accessibility

Responsive mobile-first

Vue.is

React.js

Node

NPM

Webpack

Adobe Creative cloud

Office 365

Active directory

Hardware support

VICTOR SWANBERG

Web Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sublime Media - Web Developer

2018 - Present

- Design and develop innovative web applications that draw the user's attention
- Build modular and reusable components and libraries
- Implement front-end components with progressive Vue.js framework
- Create custom stylesheets to deliver a polished designed product with CSS and SCSS
- Ensuring product works with assistive technologies
- Translate the client's technical specifications into code
- Test, update and optimize the application for performance and security

Nucamp - Instructor

2021 - Present

- Facilitate and teach online courses
- Create projects and small code environments to test users' knowledge
- Provide a positive learning experience while enforcing industry standards
- One on one's coaching with students and syntax feedback

Philip J Boren Inc. - Account Manager

2017 - 2018

- Troubleshooted any IT related issues in an corporate environment
- Maintained company website
- Deployed workstations for new employees

EDUCATION

Edmonds Community College - 2015

ATA of Computer Information Systems Desktop support specialist certificate Database management certificate Network security certificate

Nucamp - 2020

Web fundamentals certificate Front-end developer program (Bootstrap, React.js, React native) certificate